(リー)目的地は まだですか？
Are we getting close
to our destination?
At this rate, we'll get there
around noon tomorrow.
(パックン)このぶんだと 到着するのは
明日の昼頃だろう… って…➡
Stop asking me the same question
every five minutes!
５分ごとに同じ質問するのは➡
やめんかい！
わっ…。
Lee, don't be so antsy!
(テンテン)リー
焦ったって しょうがないわ。
What are you saying?! Our comrades
are anxiously waiting for us!
何を言っているんです！
里の仲間が ボクたちの到着を
心待ちにしているんですよ！
Our mission is to move at full speed
and get there as soon as possible!
熱血フルパワーで
一刻も早くたどり着くのが➡
ボクらの使命です！
(パックン)とんだ空回り野郎じゃな…。
You waste so much energy...
Shizune-senpai...
(いの)シズネ先輩。
Hmm?
If the enemy has made contact
with the Three-Tails...
敵が三尾と接触したってことは…。
That means they have a Jutsu
相手にも 三尾を手に入れる術が
あるってことですよね。
to take the Three-Tails
into their possession, right?
Yes. Probably a Sealing Jutsu,
or some Jutsu we don't know about.
(シズネ)そうね。 封印術か
私たちの知らない未知の術か…。
Once we get there, we'll have to use
our Sealing Jutsu immediately.
こっちも到着次第 すぐに
封印にとりかからないと…。
We can't have them beat us to it.
先を越されるわけにはいかないわ。
Then it's decided!
では 決まりですね！
Let's pick up our pace to twice,
no, three times the speed!
今までの２倍 いや
３倍のスピードで飛ばしましょう！
Not that nonsense again...
はぁ… また そういうムチャを…。
But I fully agree.
Pakkun, lead the way!
でも その心意気は買うわ。
パックン お願い！
Seems I have no choice.
Everyone, don't fall behind!
仕方ないな。 みんな 遅れるなよ！
(ヤマト)ハッ！
Well, that's about it.
まっ こんなもんでしょ…
どうです？ 先輩。
What do you think, Senpai?
Yeah, looks good.
(カカシ)うん いいんじゃない。
You haven't turned a page in a while.
Is something on your mind?
さっきから
全然 ページが進んでいませんね。
何か考えごとでも？
ん？
Hmm?
Oh, this and that...
まっ いろいろとね。
なぁ ヤマト。
Yamato, how do you think those guys
intended to capture the Three-Tails?
ヤツらはどうやって 三尾を捕まえる
つもりだったんだと思う？
Well, it's a Tailed Beast, after all...
そうですね。
なにぶん 相手は尾獣…。
Our opponent's Crystal Style
is powerful,
敵の晶遁は強力ですが➡
but I doubt that it's enough
to suppress the Tailed Beast...
それだけで
押さえ込める相手じゃない…。
Which means they must use
another measure concurrently.
とすると 何か並行して
他の手段を用意していた？
But back then, we weren't restrained
for very long.
(カカシ)だが あの時➡
オレたちが足止めされていた時間は
そう長くなかったはずだ。
I can't believe that they were able
その間に連中が
大掛かりな術式の準備が➡
to prepare for such
an elaborate formula in that time.
出来たとは考えにくい…。
That's true...
確かに… そういえば
ナルトが湖で子供を見たって…。
But didn't Naruto say he saw
a child by the lake?
That bothers me...
やっぱ 気になるよね…。
On top of that, we'll be facing
that Crystal Style user very soon...
それに あの晶遁使いとも➡
またすぐに やり合わなきゃ
いけないんだろうし…。
どちらへ？
Where are you going?
Let's analyze the situation and
do whatever we can now.
さしあたって
今 出来ることをね。
Kakashi-sensei...
(ヒナタ)カカシ先生…。
Let me interrupt for a little.
Hey, I want to discuss something.
ちょっと ジャマするよ。
おい 少し話をしたいんだが…。
(シノ)あぁ…。
Okay...
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and i'll never take it for granted
let's go
Everyone's Feelings
((あのね… 紅蓮さんが
ボクの帰る場所… なんだ…))
Umm... you're the one I come back to.
帰る場所か…。
Come back to... huh...?
(ナルト)アイツ…
どこにいるんだってばよ。
I wonder where he went.
コイツ… たしか木ノ葉の…。
He's from the Hidden Leaf...
これ以上 近づかれても面倒だな。
It'll be a bother if he gets any closer.
ここを動くなよ。
Don't move from this spot.
(キバ)交代の時間だぜ。
I'm here to relieve you.
(サクラ)了解。 今のところ
特に異常はないわ。
Right. So far, there's been
nothing unusual.
(サイ)あの… サクラ。
- Um... Sakura...
- Huh?
サイ？
(キバ)おい お前の担当は
ここじゃないだろ。
- Sai?
- Hey!
This isn't your position.
(サイ)いえ
それはわかっているんですが…。
Oh, I know that, but...
ナルト 知りませんか？
Do you know where Naruto is?
え？ 持ち場にいない？
Huh? Isn't he in his assigned spot?
それが 姿が見えなくて…。
Well, I don't see him.
アイツ 先に戻ったのか？
That guy, did he go back early?
だったら
途中で すれ違うはずだし…。
If so, we would've crossed paths...
そうよ。 いくらナルトだって➡
That's right. Even Naruto would
wait to be relieved of duty...!
引き継ぎくらいは… まさか…。
No way...
あの波に流されたんだ。
If that wave took him,
there wouldn't be any trace left...
やっぱ 痕跡なんて
あるわけねえか。
誰だ！
感謝しな。
Who are you?!
You should be grateful!
I came just for you.
わざわざ こちらから
出向いてやったんだ。
テメエは…。
１人で ノコノコと…。
You're...
Lurking around all by yourself...
偵察のつもりだろうが
出会った相手が悪かったね。
If your purpose was to spy,
you came across the worst opponent.
どうやら
これは幻覚じゃねえみてえだな。
It seems this is no illusion...
結晶翠晶刀！
Crystal Style: Jade Crystal Blade!
死にな！
Die!
はぁ～っ！
オレは 偵察にきたんじゃねえ。
捜しにきたんだってばよ！
I'm not spying!
I'm searching!
お前と一緒にいた あのチビをな！
For that kid who was with you!
答えろ！ アイツは どこにいる？
Answer me! Where is he?!
紅蓮さん？
Guren...?
ボク… 行かなくちゃ。
I... have to go.
なんだって!? ナルトが消えた？
What?! Naruto has disappeared?
(ヤマト)
何者かに襲撃された可能性は？
What is the possibility that
he came under attack?
現場に 怪しいニオイは
残ってなかった。
I didn't pick up
any suspicious scents at the site.
どうもアイツ 勝手に
１人で行っちまったみたいで。
I think he just took off on his own.
そういえば 何か
考え込んでたみたいだったけど➡
He seemed to have something
on his mind...
こんなことするなんて…。
But to go off like this...
ナルト君…。
まったく…。
Naruto-kun...
Geez... In any case, we have
to find Naruto at once.
とにかく早急に
ナルトを捜さないと。
じゃあ みんなで…。
(カカシ)いや 前にも言ったが➡
Then we all...
No, like I said before...
むやみに霧の中に入るのは危険だ。
It's dangerous to go
into the fog recklessly.
捜索には オレとヤマトで向かう。
Yamato and I will search for him.
(カカシ)口寄せの術！
Summoning Jutsu!
(ビスケ)
珍しいな オレが呼ばれるなんて。
It's very rare for you to summon me.
ちょっと パックンを
使いに出していてね。
Pakkun is out on a mission, so Biscuit,
I need you to find Naruto right away.
ビスケ すぐにナルトを追ってくれ。
わかった。
Gotcha.
シノとキバ ヒナタは 霧の外から➡
Shino, Kiba and Hinata
search outside the mist.
サクラとサイは
上空から探索にあたってくれ。
Sakura and Sai will do
aerial reconnaissance.
(サクラたち)はい！
絶対 単独行動はするな。
- Yes!
Do not act alone.
あのチビは どこにいる？
無事なんだろうな？
Where is the little kid?
Is he okay?!
《コイツ なぜ幽鬼丸のことを…。
This guy...
Why's he asking about Yuukimaru...?
そうか あれを見ていたのか》
I see... He was watching that...
そんなこと お前に関係ないだろ！
Well, it's none of your business!
関係あるってばよ！
フン！
It is my business!
くだらん！
So petty!
答えろ！ オレはアイツを
連れ戻さなきゃならねえんだ！
Tell me! I need to take him back!
バカじゃないのか？
連れ戻すもなにも➡
Are you crazy?
Take him back?
He was on our side from the beginning.
アイツは もともと
こっちの人間だよ。
違う！ アイツが
そっちに行っちまったのは➡
No! It's my fault that
he went over to your side!
オレのせいなんだ。 オレが
余計なことを言っちまったから。
All because of the unnecessary stuff
I said to him...
余計なこと？
Unnecessary?
ありがとう。
ボクに教えてくれたよね。
Thank you.
You taught me, didn't you?
お前…。
幽鬼丸…。
Y-You...
Yuukimaru...
思ってくれる人がいるところが
帰る場所なんだって。
Wherever someone thinks of you
is the place you go home to...
おい 動くな！
Hey, don't move!
すごく感謝してるんだ ボク。
I'm really grateful.
やっと
帰る場所が見つかったんだよ。
I finally found the place
where I can go back to.
ねっ 紅蓮さん。
Right, Guren-san?
ごめんな。
Sorry.
幽鬼丸！
動くな。
Yuukimaru!
Don't move!
影分身を１体 隠していたか。
So you were hiding one
of your Shadow Clones.
紅蓮さん！
お前 幽鬼丸っていうんだな。
Guren-san!
So your name is Yuukimaru?
オレはナルトだ。
ナルト…。
I'm Naruto.
Naruto...
幽鬼丸 お前はオレと一緒に➡
Yuukimaru, you're going home
with me to Hidden Leaf Village.
木ノ葉に帰るんだ。
どうして？
Why?
アイツは お前が帰る場所なんかじゃ
ねえからだ。
She's not the one you're going home to!
アイツは大蛇丸の手下だ。
She serves Orochimaru.
大蛇丸ってヤツは 目的のためなら
どんなことだってする。
And this guy Orochimaru will
do anything to achieve his ambition.
人の命だって
何とも思わねえ クソ野郎だ。
He's a bastard who thinks
nothing of taking peoples' lives.
そんなヤツに ついてるようなヤツが➡
Anyone who serves a guy like
that can't be a decent human being!
まともな人間なわけがねえ！
(幽鬼丸)
紅蓮さんは ボクを守ってくれる。
Guren-san will protect me...
優しくしてくれるし
思ってくれる。
She's kind to me and she thinks of me...
そんなの お前を
利用しようとしてるだけに➡
It's obvious she's just using you!
決まってんだろうが！
うるさい！
Shut up!
うわっ！
コイツは お前のところには帰らない。
(幽鬼丸)紅蓮さん。
This kid won't return to your place!
Guren-san...
《何か来る…。
Something's coming...
木ノ葉のヤツらか》
The Hidden Leaf...
腕ずくでも連れ帰るってばよ！
I'm taking him by force, if necessary!
結晶六角手裏剣乱舞！
Hexagonal Crystal Shuriken:
Wild Dance!
うわっ！ うっ！
なに!?
くらえ！
What?!
Take this!
うわっ！
逃がすか！ うっ…。
I won't let you get away!
(カカシ)ナルト！ そこまでだ。
Naruto, stop!
フゥ… 確保完了。
Stabilized and secured.
離してくれってばよ！
オレは アイツを…。
Let me go!
I'm taking him...!
ムダだ。 ヤツらは もう消えたよ。
It's no use. They've disappeared.
クソッ…。
Damn it...
((アイツは大蛇丸の手下だ。
(人の命だって
何とも思わない クソ野郎だ))
She serves Orochimaru.
He's a bastard who thinks
nothing of taking peoples' lives.
(牛頭)紅蓮さん おケガは？
Guren-san, are you hurt?
余計なことするな！
Don't bother me!
((アイツは お前が帰る
場所なんかじゃねえからだ))
She's not the one you're going home to.
《あのガキ 今度会ったら…》
That kid... When I see him again...
(牛頭)すみませんでした。 でも➡
I'm sorry... But...
あなたが無事で よかった。
I'm glad you're all right.
ハァ… ハァ…。
幽鬼丸！
Yuukimaru!
オレは帰るぞ。
あぁ ご苦労さま。
I'm going back.
Right. Thanks.
(ヤマト)どういうつもりだ？
勝手に行動すれば➡
What's with you?
あの晶遁使いと出くわす可能性が
あることくらい➡
Surely, you knew that if
you went off on your own,
you were bound to encounter
that Crystal Style user?
わかってたろ？
それは…。
でも オレ どうしてもアイツを…。
I know.
But I... I just had to find him...
言い訳は よせ！
運が悪ければ 今ごろキミは
死んでいたかもしれない。
Don't make excuses.
You're lucky; you could've
been dead by now.
感情で動いて
仲間たちを危険にさらして！
You put your comrades in danger
because you gave in to your emotions.
こんなことで キミを信じて
任務に出してくれた綱手様に➡
How can you face Tsunade-sama,
顔向けできるのかい？
who put her trust in you and
sent you on this mission?
悪かったってばよ。
Okay, I was wrong.
今回の任務は どう転ぶか
わからない危険な代物だ。
This mission involves a dangerous,
unpredictable foe.
個人の勝手な行動は
仲間を全滅させることもある。
Recklessly acting on your own
could spell death for everyone.
そのことを肝に銘じておけ。
あぁ。
Don't let yourself forget that.
じゃあ 戻りますか。
そうだな。
Yeah.
Shall we return?
ところでナルト… お前
湖で子供を見たって言ってたな。
Yes.
By the way, Naruto,
you said you saw a child at the lake.
え… それが？
気になることがある。
Huh? What about it?
その時のこと
もう少し詳しく聞かせてくれ。
Something's been bothering me.
Tell me the details of that incident.
(麟児)紅蓮さん よくご無事で…。
Guren-san! I'm glad you're okay.
すんません。 湖の近くじゃ
オレの探索網が使えなくて…。
Sorry. But I couldn't use my search net
near the lake.
まぁいい。
どうやら こっちの戦力は
欠けてないようだね。
Forget it... It seems we haven't
lost any fighting strength...
若干１名 欠けたほうが
よかったヤツもいるけどな。
Although, there's at least one
I would've preferred to lose.
悪運が強いのは お互いさまだろ。
So I'm blessed with the luck of evil.
It's mutual.
少し弱っているが許容範囲だな。
He's weakened, but it's tolerable.
疲れているんだ 休ませてやれ。
(カブト)残念だけど➡
He's exhausted. Let him rest.
ボクたちも そうのんびり
構えていられないみたいでね。
Unfortunately...
I don't think we can afford to
hang around here.
どう考えても 連中が三尾を
捕獲するという大事な場面に➡
I just can't imagine why those guys
would take an ordinary kid along,
ただの子供を連れていくとは
考えにくくてな。
when they face a huge challenge
in snaring the Three-Tails.
ただの子供じゃないって…。
He's no ordinary kid, I tell you...
例えば 三尾に対して何らかの
強制力を持っているとか…。
What if he possesses some
special power against the Three-Tails?
そういえば…。
アイツが何かしたら
三尾の動きが止まったような…。
Now that you mention it...
He did something and...
it seemed as though
the Three-Tails stopped moving.
やはりか…。
人間が尾獣をコントロールしてた
ってことですか。
It figures...
You mean a human was
controlling a Tailed Beast?
どんな手を使ったか知らないが
相手は あの大蛇丸だからな。
I don't know what trick they used,
but we're dealing with Orochimaru...
連中が子供を使って
三尾を捕獲する気なのは➡
It's probably no mistake
間違いないだろう。
that they intend to use a child
to capture the Three-Tails.
だとすると その子 このまま
放っておくわけにはいきませんね。
Which means, this child...
We can't just ignore him.
それって どういう意味だよ？
スキを見て こちらで拘束する。
拘束？
What do you mean by that?
We wait for an opportunity,
and then we take him.
(カカシ)子供さえいなければ➡
Take him?
連中が三尾を手に入れる手段は
ないからね。
As long as they don't have the boy,
they have no method to
capture the Three-Tails.
(ヤマト)それに大蛇丸が ただ三尾を
手に入れて満足するとは思えない。
And I can't believe that
Orochimaru will be satisfied with
just capturing Three-Tails...
遅かれ早かれ➡
自分にとって扱いやすい
人柱力を作ろうと考えるはずだ。
Sooner or later,
he'll think of ways to create
a Jinchuriki that is easy to control.
ヤツにとって 尾獣との
適応能力の高い子供は➡
For him, a boy with the ability
to synergize with a Tailed Beast
格好の素材になりかねない。
is merely a useful tool.
そんなこと させてたまっかよ！
I won't let him do that!
当然だ。
それに 里としても今後のため➡
You're absolutely right.
Besides, I'm sure they would want
to examine his powers back at the village.
彼の能力を調査しておきたいしな。
《まぁ すべては綱手様からの
返答があってからだが…》
Well, it all depends
on Tsunade-sama's reply.
ナルト!!
サクラちゃん！
Naruto!
クッ…。
Sakura!
これが 愛のムチってヤツか。
This is... the loving smack?
オレたちが説教するより
よっぽど効果的だな これは。
This is far more effective
than us trying to lecture him.
カカシ先生 ナルトには
キツく言い聞かせましたから。
Kakashi-sensei,
I gave Naruto an earful.
ちゃんと反省してた？
Was he sorry?
ご… ごめんなさい。
I'm so-sorry...
それより 朗報です。
木ノ葉の増援が？
Never mind that.
There's good news!
敵ながら対応が早い。 おそらく
ヤツら 三尾を封じにかかるだろう。
Reinforcements from the Hidden Leaf?
Our foes respond very quickly.
No doubt, they will try to seal
the Three-Tails.
冗談じゃない
三尾は大蛇丸様のものだ！
No way! The Three-Tails belongs
to Lord Orochimaru.
当然だよ。 だから紅蓮➡
Of course!
And that is why, this time, Guren...
キミには幽鬼丸を使って
今度こそ三尾をおさえてもらう。
You must use Yuukimaru
to suppress the Three-Tails.
しかし まだ幽鬼丸は…。
But Yuukimaru is still...
心配ない。 体力を底上げして
少し休ませれば また使えるさ。
Don't worry. If we build up his stamina
and allow him to rest a bit,
we'll be able to use him.
《また あの薬を飲ませるのか…》
He's going to give him that drug again...
だが 見たところ 幽鬼丸は
かなり衰弱しているようだ。
But Yuukimaru still looks awfully weak.
ムリをさせて ホントに大丈夫なのか？
If you force him...
Are you sure he'll be all right?
さぁ どうかな？
Well, I wonder...
そんなに怖い顔をするなよ。
キミだって承知しているはずだ。
Don't look at me like that.
幽鬼丸は
三尾を操作するためだけの道具。
You should know that Yuukimaru
is simply a tool to capture the Three-Tails.
今がんばってもらわないと
存在自体 意味がない。
Unless we make use of him now,
there's no meaning in
his very existence.
だが 今コイツが ぶっ壊れたら
計画は お釈迦になって…。
But if he collapses and the plan fails...
私の信用は まるつぶれだ！
My credibility will be totally ruined!
紅蓮 ボクだって
この計画の成功を望んでいるのさ。
Guren, I'm hoping that
the plan is a success.
だからこそ こうして…。
That's why I...
ムカツクねぇ！
だいたいアンタ
人の仕事に口出しすぎなんだよ！
Well, it's irritating.
You tend to stick your nose into
other people's business too often.
紅蓮… お前…。
Guren... You...
要は木ノ葉に三尾を
封印させなきゃいいんだろ。
The main thing is to prevent
the Hidden Leaf from sealing
the Three-Tails, right?
だったら 私が木ノ葉の連中を
殲滅してやる！
Well then, I'll destroy the Leaf!
もめたんですかい？
あのクソメガネ もともと
気にくわないんだよ ったく！
Had an argument?
I've never liked that four-eyed jerk!
幽鬼丸を殺す気なのか？
Does he want to kill Yuukimaru?
へぇ～。
Oh...
何だ!?
意外ですねぇ。
What?
紅蓮さんが
幽鬼丸の心配をするなんて。
It's unlike you to worry
so much about Yuukimaru.
ハッ バカ言うんじゃないよ。 私はただ
任務の心配をしているだけだ。
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just concerned about our mission.
任務の心配ねぇ…。
Concerned about the mission, eh...?
増援が来たって 誰だってばよ？
(サクラ)まぁ 見ての お楽しみよ。
Reinforcements are here? Who?
Just wait and see.
もうダメじゃ… １歩も走れん。
I've had it... I can't run any further.
サクラちゃん 援軍って…。
Sakura-chan, who's come to help...?
(いの)ナルト！
アンタ またムチャやったんだって？
You're so reckless, Naruto!
ドンマイです！
青春に ムチャはつきものです！
It's okay! Recklessness and youth
go hand in hand!
はい そこ！ 肯定しない！
Stop affirming his actions!
あっ！ お前ら！
Hey! You guys...!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
oh my god oh my god
yesterday's mistake got me discouraged, but
kinou no shippai de kojiketatte
Thank you! Thank you!
gottsuanda gottsuanda
my new clothes got splashed with some sauce, wow
onyuu no fuku ni sousu ga hanete wao
don't mind, don't mind, if I stay feeling like this I'll have a tear in my eyes
donmai donmai shizunda mama ja namida mo my eyes
I may be hungry and angry
donna ni hangurii de angurii demo
but I'll grab a bowl to eat and start dancing!
donburi kutte danshingu
We'll always be pals my brother!
orera itsumo demo nakama daro burazaa
hit me with an upwind or strong wind or a storm I'm ready so come on!
tatoe gyarufuu kyoufuu arashi ga fuitemo bacchikoi kamon
we may be apart but we'll still be under the same sky
hanaretetemo onaji sora no shita de
so smile and hang on
saa waratte funbatte
lets do it do it do it do it
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
even if morning doesn't come, yay yay
tatoe asa ga konakutatte yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
we'll still watch the dream together, yay yay
kimi to tomo ni yume wo miru ze yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
no matter what, don't ever, ever give up, yay yay
nani ga nandemo aa demo kou demo akirameru na yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
morning will always come after night, yay yay
donna yoru mo asa wa kuru ze yay yay
nanananana
Next Episode
Let me go over Tsunade-sama's orders.
Our new mission is to seal
the Tailed Beast, the Three-Tails.
And, to protect the child
from the enemy.
He seems to be connected
in some way to this Tailed Beast!
With the mission change,
you'll be divided into the following teams.
Sealing team, Guarding team
and the Crystal User Counter team.
Got it. And, how will we team up for this?
Yeah, about that... I have an idea.
Regroup!
Next time: "Regroup!"
Kakashi, I'm back now.
ハァ ハァ…。 カカシ 今戻ったぞ。
Oh, thanks.
"Oh thanks"? Can't you put
more appreciation into your reply?
あぁ ご苦労。
ご苦労って…。
In addition to my appreciation,
could you deliver another message?
感謝の気持を込めて言っても
バチは当たらんだろう。
じゃあ 感謝ついでに悪いけど➡
Hey! Can't you be more kind to me?!
もう ひとっ走り
伝令を頼まれてくれないか？
Kakashi-sensei.
コラッ もっとワシをいたわらんか。
If you don't mind,
you can also use my
"Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll."
カカシ先生。 よかったら
ボクの超獣偽画を使ってください。
Huh?!
Information drawn by my ink
will change into small animals,
ボクが墨で書いた情報は
小動物のように変化し➡
protect themselves,
and deliver messages outside.
自分の身を守りながら 情報を外へ
持ち出してくれますから。
Oh, that's handy.
Then let's get to it.
- Wait a minute!
- Huh?
ほぅ ソイツは便利だな。 では 早速。
You can't trust scribble like that!
ちょっと待った！
ん？
I'll show you what
Ninja Hounds are made of!
そんな落書き 信用できるか！
I won't let an ink bird
take my chance to show off!
忍犬のほうが 優れておるところを
見せてやるわい！
《せっかくの拙者の出番➡
Oh no. He's off...
あんな墨鳥に取られてたまるか》
Did I do something wrong?
あ～ぁ 行っちゃった。
No. It's for the best.
ボク なにか悪いことしました？
Huh?
いや 結果オーライってことで。 ん？
Oh no!
"MAKE-OUT PARADISE BEST QUOTE COLLECTION"
I gave him the wrong scroll!
《しまった。 渡すの間違えた》